The perfect push up can take place anywhere.
We're going to do it out here on the ground.
Starting with your knees.
This is a beginner level.
But, hold tight, I'll show you some other variations.
First, make sure your arms are about shoulder width apart.
Your hips are down.
Not too low and not too high.
Just in the middle.
You're going to bend at your elbows.
Don't touch the ground. Your head is looking down. Exhale and extend. Pressing through your palms back up. That's one rep. Inhale, down, exhale, up.
Inhale, down, exhale, up.
You're going to feel this in your triceps, the back of your arms.
Everything nice and tight and in through your chest.
Now with the outdoors, you might feel that you need to get hyped up and do a little bit more.
So, I'm going to take you to your toes.
This is intermediate.
Still come down, exhale up.
It?s going to be a little tougher but you can do it.
Inhale down and exhale up.
Now if you feel like you still want more of a challenge, bring your hands in, on your toes, and go out to the side, together.
And then to the other side and together.
Alright.
You can work to this.
So let's do three more, two and one.
That's your push up.